{
  "results": [
    {
      "question": "Which part of Mars' surface seems older?",
      "correct_answer": "southern hemisphere",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "equator",
        "northern hemisphere",
        "polar caps",
        "southern hemisphere"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which color are sunsets on Mars?",
      "correct_answer": "blue",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "green",
        "red",
        "blue",
        "orange"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "TARs are features that are only seen on Mars. What is the best definition of TARs?",
      "correct_answer": "crestless sand dunes up to 15 meters high",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "large volcanoes up to 15 kilometers tall",
        "large mountains up to 15 kilometers tall",
        "huge craters about 15 meters wide",
        "crestless sand dunes up to 15 meters high"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The chances are high that there used to be oceans and rivers on Mars:",
      "correct_answer": "true, about 4 billion years ago",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "false, but rains may have infiltrated in the soil",
        "false, never",
        "true, about 4 million years ago",
        "true, about 4 billion years ago"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which part of Mars has lower elevation and once had oceans?",
      "correct_answer": "northern hemisphere",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "equator",
        "northern hemisphere",
        "polar caps",
        "southern hemisphere"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What year was Mars discovered?",
      "correct_answer": "1659",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1543",
        "1659",
        "1770",
        "1790"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Mars distance from the earth?",
      "correct_answer": "54.6 million kilometers",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "98.0 million kilometers",
        "76.2 million kilometers",
        "66.7 million kilometers",
        "54.6 million kilometers"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "How long can it take you to travel to Mars from Earth in light speed?",
      "correct_answer": "12.5 light minutes",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "11.8 light minutes",
        "12.5 light minutes",
        "14.1 light minutes",
        "16.2 light minutes"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "How much is Mars' diameter in comparison with the earth's diameter?",
      "correct_answer": "half of the earth’s diameter",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "twice the earth’s diameter",
        "equal with the earth’s diameter",
        "half of the earth’s diameter",
        "quarter of the earth’s diameter"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these fields is absent in Mars?",
      "correct_answer": "both",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "magnetic",
        "soccer",
        "neither",
        "both"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "How many moons does Mars have?",
      "correct_answer": "2",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "4",
        "3",
        "2",
        "1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "How many moons does Mars have?",
      "correct_answer": "2",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "4",
        "3",
        "2",
        "1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the names of Mars' moons?",
      "correct_answer": "phobos and deimos",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "miranda and titania",
        "phobos and deimos",
        "ganymede and callisto",
        "pallas and vesta"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Mars gets it red color from what?",
      "correct_answer": "oxidation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "red paint",
        "ultraviolet radiation",
        "oxidation",
        "asteroid bombardment"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who discovered Mars' moons?",
      "correct_answer": "asaph hall",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "galileo",
        "johannes kepler",
        "isaac newton",
        "asaph hall"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What do the names of the Martian satellites mean?",
      "correct_answer": "fear and panic",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "peace and hope",
        "panic and hatred",
        "fear and hatred",
        "fear and panic"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the gravity of Mars as compared to Earth?",
      "correct_answer": ".379:1",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        ".379:1",
        ".254:1",
        ".750:1",
        ".563:1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the name of the mission that landed spacecraft on Mars in the 70's?",
      "correct_answer": "viking",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "pioneer",
        "pathfinder",
        "viking",
        "mariner"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The temperature at the poles of Mars is about:",
      "correct_answer": "-190 degrees F",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "-350 degrees F",
        "-190 degrees F",
        "-100 degrees F",
        "-40 degrees F"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "If you weighed 150 pounds on Earth, how much would you weigh on Mars?",
      "correct_answer": "57 pounds",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "12 pounds",
        "26 pounds",
        "57 pounds",
        "150 pounds"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the diameter of Mars?",
      "correct_answer": "4,200 miles",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2,100 miles",
        "4,200 miles",
        "7,600 miles",
        "7,900 miles"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the tilt of Mars' axis?",
      "correct_answer": "25.19 degrees",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "21.83 degrees",
        "22.17 degrees",
        "23.69 degrees",
        "25.19 degrees"
      ]
    }
  ]
}